ROBERT ISAAC EBITA CORTEZ

Front End Web Developer

- Prk. Cawayan, Brgy. Cebuano, Tupi, South Cotabato, 9505. Philippines
- +63 985 652 8649
- isaacebitacortez@gmail.com



ABOUT ME

As a former student nurse turned web developer, Isaac's resume highlights his transferable skills from nursing education and business administration, such as problem-solving, communication, and presentation skills, secretarial experience, volunteer work, current education and skills in web development, and personal projects and achievements.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Canva

Presentation Skills, Counseling Skills, Clerical Skills, Problem-Solving Skills, Graphic Design Skills

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Outlook, Powerpoint)

LINKS

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/robert-isaac -ebita-cortez-376320310

GitHub

https://github.com/lsaacCortezUIU Χ

Portfolio

https://amnesiaproductions.netlify.

LANGUAGES

English

Filipino

Hiligaynon

HOBBIES

Interested in Rock Climbing, Graphic Design, Manga,

COURSEWORK

- Sydney, NSW, Australia **NURSING COURSEWORK**
 - completed coursework in Anatomy, Physiology, Epidemiology, Patient Care, and Mental Health Nursing at University of Technology Sydney - enhanced skills in communication and critical thinking skills

Online

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

- completed coursework in Basic Programming and Information Literacy at Mapua Malayan Digital College
- enhanced skills in analysis, logic and critical thinking

WORK EXPERIENCE

RS Cortez: Fresh & Frozen South Cotabato

FEB 2018 - FEB 2019

SECRETARY

- · Managed administrative tasks for a family business specializing in wholesale delivery of seafood goods.
- · Coordinated orders and deliveries of commercial seafood products, including salmon, milkfishes, and yellowfin tuna.
- · Handled customer inquiries and ensured timely and accurate delivery of goods.
- · Developed strong organizational and clerical skills in a fast-paced business environment.

Various Hospitals Sydney

DEC 2020 - MAY 2021

STUDENT NURSE PLACEMENTS

- · Bankstown Hospital (Stroke and Rehabilitation): Assisted in patient care and rehabilitation programs for geriatric stroke patients (Bankstown NSW, December 2020)
- · Bankstown Hospital (Endocrinology): Supported the medical team in managing patients with endocrine disorders (Bankstown NSW, February 2021)
- · Croydon Community Health Centre (Community Mental Health): Participated in community visits and mental health support programs (Croydon, May 2021)

Zion Christian Misson Center

FEB 2020 - FEB 2023

Sydney

VOLUNTEER STAFF

- · Assisted in organizing and coordinating community church events at a branch church.
- · Engaged with community members to foster a welcoming environment.
- · Developed presentation and counseling skills through event participation.
- · Initiated counseling sessions and spiritual discussions with guests
- · Scouted potential theology students to study 8-10 month

EDUCATION

Uplift Code Camp

2024

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP

- working towards training and certification as a Full Stack Web Developer
- includes projects and activities utilizing HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS, Tailwind, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB

UTS College Sydney

UTS-COLLEGE FOUNDATION STUDIES

Notre Dame of Marbel University - Integrated Basic Education Department

2018

2020

Koronadal City, South Cotabato HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

- Graduated with honors (Average of 91)